https://www.assistnews.net/privacy

December 6, 2020
Armenian Christian holy sites desecrated in Nagorno-Karabakh conflict
November 29, 2020
Top Christian Ministers Harassed, Threatened After Moving to…
November 26, 2020
Coping with COVID-era holiday loneliness
November 26, 2020
Uptick in Egyptian Arrests Highlights Continued Crackdown on…
December 3, 2020
Indonesian Terrorist Group Behind Salvation Army Attack Identified
November 6, 2019
Strawberry Field – Major Kathy Versfeld (Podcast)
September 3, 2019
Peter Wooding – Following Dad’s Footsteps (Podcast)
August 20, 2019
Bryn Yemm – Welsh Singer from the Valleys…
July 29, 2019
Kathy Green – A Woman of Steel (Podcast)
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Get ASSIST Updates
Individual
Media Outlet
Leave this field empty if you're human:
Support Assist News
Search
The Latest
Gifts that Keep on Giving:
Being the Hands, and Feet, and Voice of Jesus
December 9, 2020
Hope In the Midst of Lockdowns
December 7, 2020
Vision & Mission
No "fake news" here. The Gospel is our motivation. Our passion is to glorify God by reporting on World Missions, the persecuted church, and stories and events that inspire our daily lives for Christ.
ANS was founded by Dan Wooding to inform, educate, and inspire about all that God is doing in today's culture. Assist News mobilizes Christians to intervene on behalf of the persecuted church.
Follow Us On Facebook Facebook
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.				Accept Read More
Get Updates in Your Inbox
Individual
Media Outlet
Leave this field empty if you're human:
X
